question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "'Typewriter' is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Coca-Cola's original colour was green.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "There are 86400 seconds in a day.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The word 'news' originates from the first letters of the 4 main directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The average woman is 5 inches ~13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The term 'Spam' came before the food product 'Spam'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person's life expectancy.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The French word to travel is 'Travail'",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The French word for 'glass' is glace.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Fast food restaurant chains Carl's Jr. and Hardee's are owned by the same company.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Francis Bacon died from a fatal case of pneumonia while he was attempting to preserve meat by stuffing a chicken with snow.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "'Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo'  is a grammatically correct sentence.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
